MD Arif Howlader

04 road, Rony Market, Dhaka 01757072833 mdarif13131@gmail.com

03 January, 2022

Chairman

Aloron School and College Rony market, Kamrangir Char, Dhaka

Dear Sir,

I am very interested in applying for a teaching position in your school. I would like to apply as Teacher in science Level in your school. I have experienced in teaching for one year. I hope that I will continue my teaching career in your school.

Teaching in school is a challenge for me. School gives basic skills for students. I have worked in Asuliya City School And College. I implemented Essential Academic Learning Requirements concept in lesson planning and contributed in Character Education curriculum. I have successfully developed teaching in interdisciplinary units and developed proactive elassroom.

I am a student in Sonargoan University Department of CSE. I am capable of problem solving in crucial cases. I am able to handle my students properly in a classroom. I am able to use interesting teaching method that makes students focus on my lesson. Recently my university physical class started so I want to join in your school teacher panel.

I am sure that my skills and experiences are switable with your job requirements. I am so happy if I get a chance to meet you for further selection process. Do not hesitate to contact me at(call 01757072833, WhatsApp - 01757072833, mail - arifhossen13131@gmail.com) . Thank you for your attention.

Sincerely, Md Arif Howlader Student of Sonargoan University

Md Arif



MD Arif Howlader

E-mail: arifhossen13131@gmail.com Phone: 01757072833

Address: Permanent address: Barishal, Bakergong,

Faridpur,Ragunaddi,Janatar Hat, Present address: Rony market, 4 no road, Kamrangir Char, Dhaka

Work experience

Asuliya City School And College

08 March 2020 — 25 December 2021

Teacher

- Effectively taught Physics, Chemistry and Higher math to 9-10 class students and maintained interest enabling students significantly hone learning skills.
- Guided and counseled students with adjustment or academic problems , or special academic interests .
- · I know how teach and control students .
- · Have knowledge of Students development .
- · Have experience to work field side for increase student .

SSC care, Barishal

01 January 2020 — 05 March 2020

Tutor

- •Have 2 month experience teaching Coaching centre.
- •I took class SSC coaching centre in Barishal City.
- ·I taught Physics.

Education

BSc in CSE Department

03 January 2021 — Present

Sonargaon University

Now I am a student of Sonargoan University Department of CSE.

HSC 2016 — 2019

Hellal Uddin Ahmed Degree College

- *I passed my HSC in 2019 with GPA 4.58 from science group.
- * I was Rover Scout group mate in my College so I know how to maintain time, rules and programme.

SSC 2014 — 2016

Hazi Panchom Ali Secondary School

I passed SSC in 2016 with GPA 4.78 from Science group.

Scanned with CamScanner



MD Arif Howlader

E-mail: arifhossen13131@gmail.com Phone: 01757072833

Address: Permanent address: Barishal, Bakergong,

Faridpur,Ragunaddi,Janatar Hat, Present address: Rony market, 4 no road, Kamrangir Char, Dhaka

Skills

- Creativity
- · Schedule Management
- Effective Communication
- · Leadership
- · Handling Pressure
- · Motivation Speaker

Summary

Adaptable professional with about 1 Years of experience and proven knowledge of classroom management, course design and curriculum development. An enthusiastic educator who understands for students to gain physical skills and confidence for their all - round education to succeed. Looking to contribute my knowledge and skills in an institution that offers a genuine opportunity for career progression

MD Aril Howlader





Ashulia City School & College



Name : Md. Arif Howlader

Designation: Senior Teacher (Science)

Blood Group: B+

Cell : 01757-072833

100



গণপ্রজাতন্ত্রী বাংলাদেশ সরকার

Government of the People's Republic of Bangladesh জাতীয় পরিচয়পত্র / National ID Card

05 Sep 2000



নায়

মোঃ আরিফ হাওলাদার

Name

MD. ARIF HOWLADER

199

মোঃ শাহ আলম হাওলাদার

মাত

হোসনেয়ারা বেগম

Date of Birth 05 Sep 2000

NID No.

871 284 8475



CHILASO



ঠিকানা: বাসা/হোল্ডিং: হাওলাদা বাড়ী, গ্রাম/রাস্তা: পশ্চিম চর রঘুনাথিদি, ডাকঘর: জনতারহাট - ৮৬২৩, বাকেরগঞ্জ, বরিশাল



Blood Group: B+ Place of Birth: BARISAL

Issue Date: 27 Nov 2020

I<BGD871284847<50<<<<<<<<< 0009058M3511266BGD<<<<<<<< HOWLADER<<MD<ARIF<<<<<<<

BOARD OF INTERMEDIATE AND SECONDARY EDUCATION, BARISAI BANGLADESH



Secondary School Certificate Examination 2016

Serial No. BBAT 1621021

ACADEMIC TRANSCRIPT

BBAT No: 160-219444

Graie	Class Interval	Grade Point	
A+	80 100	5	
A	10.79	4	
Α.	6.) 49	3.5	
В	50-59	3	
(40.49	2	
D	33-19	1	
F	0.32	0	

Name of Student : Md. Arif Howlader

Father's Name : Md. Shah Alam Howlader

Mother's Name : Hosneara Begum

Name of Institution: Hazi Pancham Ali Secondary School, Patuakhali

Name of Centre : Kalishuri (322) Type : Regular

Roll Number : 138454 Registration No.: 1315473597/2014-15

Group : Science Date of Birth : 05/09/2000

Sl. No.	Name of Subjects	Letter Grade	Grade Point	GPA Without which bend solvent	GPA
1	Bangla	A	4.0		
2	English	A	4.0		
3	Mathematics	A	4.0		
4	Bangladesh & Global Studies	A	4.0		
5	Reli.& Moral Education (Isl)	A+	5.0	4.56	4.78
6	Physics	A+	5.0		
7	Chemistry	A+	5.0		
8	Biology	A+	5.0		
9	Physical Edu., Health & Sports	A+	5.0		
10	additional Subject: Higher Mathematics	A	4.0	GP above 2 2.00	

A controller of Examinations

Date of Publication of Result: 11 May, 2016

Scanned with CamScanner

BOARD OF INTERMEDIATE AND SECONDARY EDUCATION, BARISAL

BANGLADESH

Higher Secondary Certificate Examination, 2019

Serial No. BBAT 1671927

ACADEMIC TRANSCRIPT

BBHAT No :190-016033

Grade	Class Interval	Grade Point
A+	80-100	5
A	70-79	4
Α-	60-69	3.5
В	50-59	3
С	40-49	2
D	33-39	1
F	0-32	0

: Md. Arif Howlader Name of Student

: Md. Shah Alam Howlader Father's Name

: Hosneara Begum Mother's Name

Name of Institution: Helaluddin College (100594)

Type: Improvement : Kakordha (164) Name of Centre

Registration No.: 1315473597/2016-2017 : 602118 Roll Number

: Science Group

Sl. No	Name of Subjects	Letter Grade	Grade Point	Marks	(Without additional subject)	GPA
1	Bangla	A-	3.5	137		
2	English	A-	3.5	136		
3	Physics	A+	5.0	173	1 22	4.58
4	Chemistry	A	4.0	150	4.33	4.50
	Higher Mathematics	A+	5.0	173		
6	Information & Communication Technology	A+	5.0	086		
	Additional Subject : Biology	A-	3.5	136	GP above 2 1.50	



Date of Publication of Result: 17th July, 2019

✓ Controller of Examinations